A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness House drawings, SG 2 FA247
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Second Floor/Mezzanine, 1906-1982; 4
  - Building/Floor Plans, 4.1
    - Library
      - 2/5/1908, 350 NY 33 (Folder 87)
        North Elevation of Library, Plan of Shelf, Plan of Soffit, # 1-33 5/8"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-Paper Size-36 7/8"x30 1/4", Image Size-33 1/2"x17", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 7/17/1908, 1095 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 74 Second Copy Doesn't Have Office Copy # (Folder 88)
        Plan and Detail of Marble Base in Library, Second Floor, Section of Base,, # 1- 24 3/8"x23 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Plan Library, 24 3/8"x22 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Hall/Stair Hall/Elevator Vestibule
      - undated, Revised 4/21/1908; Drawing Number 26 (Folder 89)
        Drawing in 2 Sections, Plan and Elevations of Stairs, Second to Mezz. Floors, Elevation of North Wall, Elevation of South Wall, Section, A-A, Section B-B, Section C-C, Section D-D, Written on the Back in Pencil (Larger Section), Traitel's Drawings of Stairs to Mezz Floor, (Larger Section) @ 43 1/2"x27", (Smaller Section) 15 1/8"x4 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - 2/5/1908, 343 NY 33 (Folder 90)
        Plan of Second Story Hall, Half Plan of Floor, Half Plan of Ceiling, #1-35 1/2"x21", Tracing Paper, # 2-36 1/8"x21 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/6/1908, 344 NY 33 (Folder 90)
        Elevation of Second Story Hall, Half Elevation of South Side, Half Elevation of North Side, General Notes on the Right Side, # 1-40 3/8"x21 1/8", Linen, # 2-40 1/2"x21 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 1981 July 10, 345 NY 33 (Folder 90)
        End Elevation of Second Story Hall and Plan and Elevation of Elevator Vestibule, West Elevation of Hall, Plan of Elevator Vestibule and North Elevation of Elevator Vestibule, # 1-36 3/4"x21 1/8", Linen, # 2-35 3/4"x21 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 932 (Office Copy) T3 (Folder 91)
        Second Platform, First and Second Floors, 11 7/8"x7 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        Received 6/10/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 933 (Office Copy) T2 (Folder 91)
        Platform, Second to Mezzanine Floors, 11 1/4"x7 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, 934 (Office Copy) T4 (Folder 91)
        Mezzanine Floor Landing, 18"x9 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, 1017 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 56 Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy Number or an Order # (Folder 92)
        Full Scale Drawings Showing Finish of Wainscot Cap Over Windows on Stairs, Mezzanine to Third Floors, Section, # 1-Witten on the Back in Pen, Stairwell —>, Written on the Back in Pencil, 3rd Floor Window Molding, 28 1/2"x@ 19 5/8", # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Drawing of Finish of Wainscot Cap Over Window, Mezz to Third Floors, 26"x19 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        Received 6/15/1908 Charles T. Wills #2-Received 6/30/1908 Charles T. Wills
      - 6/22/1908-7/1/1908, 1022 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 57 Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy # (Folder 92)
        Plan of Marble Base Around Second Floor Hall, # 1-Written on the Back in Pen, Marble Base, 32 3/8"x18 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Detail of Marble Base in Second Story Hall, 30 1/4"x16", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        #1-6/22/1908 #2-6/22/1908, Revised 7/1/1908
      - undated, 1074 (Office Copy) (Folder 92)
        Plan of the Second Floor, 20 1/2"x16", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Probably Hale and Rogers)
      - undated, 1075 (Office Copy) (Folder 92)
        Plan of the Mezzanine Story, 20 1/2"x16", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Probably Hale and Rogers)
      - 7/28/1908, 1110 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 78 Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy # (Folder 93)
        Plan of Marble Base, Second Floor Elevator Vestibule, Full Scale Section Thro' Marble Base, # 1-16 1/2"x14 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel Plan of Marble Base, Second Story, Elevator Vestibule, 16 1/2"x14 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - 1/17/1908, Order Number 1770, Plan Number 8 (Folder 93)
        Stairs to Third Floor, Elevation "A-A", Section "B-B", Section "C-C", Details-Stairs to the 4th Floor, Written on the Back in Pencil, Hennibique Stair: Details-Stairs to the 3rd Floor, @ 25 3/4"x24", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hennibique Construction Co.
      - 1970 March 9, P-65, 915 (Folder 89)
        Elevator Vestibule, Second Story, Plan, North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation and West Elevation, 25 1/4"x45 1/8", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
    - Music Room
      - 7/23/1912, 301A NY 33 (Folder 94)
        Alteration to Music Room Mantel, # 1-26 1/2"x18 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-25 3/4"x18 3/8', Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 7/24/1920, 301 NY 376 (Folder 94)
        South Elevation of Music Room, 33 1/4"x23 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Possibly James Gamble Rogers)
      - 7/24/1920, 302 NY 376 (Folder 94)
        West Elevation of Music Room, 34 1/4"x23 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Possibly James Gamble Rogers)
      - 7/24/1920, 303 NY 376 (Folder 94)
        North Elevation of Music Room, Plan of Fireplace, 34 1/8"x23 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Possibly James Gamble Rogers)
      - 7/24/1920, 304 NY 376 (Folder 94)
        East Elevation of Music Room, 34"x23 1/2", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Possibly James Gamble Rogers)
      - 7/24/1920, 305 NY 376 (Folder 95)
        Ceiling Plan, Music Room, 20 3/4"x18", Tracing Paper, Architects, O.F. (Drawn By) (Possibly of Hale and Rogers)
      - 2/5/1908, 351 NY 33 (Folder 95)
        Plan Music Room, Half Plan of Floor, Half Plan of Ceiling, # 1-27 1/4"x26 1/2", Tracing Paper, #2-27 1/2"x32 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 352 NY 33 (Folder 95)
        East Elevation, Music Room, # 1-31 1/2"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-Paper Size-34 5/8"x30 1/4", Image Size-31 1/8"x17 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 353 NY 33 (Folder 96)
        North Elevation, Music Room, # 1-31"x17 3/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-31 1/8"x17 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 354 NY 33 (Folder 96)
        West Elevation, Music Room, Detailed Note on the Right Side, # 1-31"x17 3/8", Tracing Paper, #2-31 1/8"x17 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 355 NY 33 (Folder 96)
        South Elevation, Music Room, # 1-31"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 7/8"x17 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 6/26/1917, 601 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 601,#718 (Folder 97)
        Circassian Walnut, 4 Window Trims and Base, Alterations in Music Room, (In 4 Pieces) # 1- (Top) 38"x18 1/4", # 2- (Bottom) 41 1/4"x17 3/4", # 3-6 1/4"x4", # 4-4"x3", # 5-9 1/4"X9 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - 1981 August 7, 601 (Office Copy), Order Number 5517, Drawing Number 2 (Folder 98)
        Mantel in Music Room, Written Back in Pencil, Harkness Res., Our Drawing #2, 2 Prints to James Gamble Rogers for Approval, 17 1/2"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - 6/26/1917, 602 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 602, #718 (Folder 97)
        Circassian Walnut/Door Trim, Alterations in Music Room, (In 2 Pieces) # 1-47 1/2"x55 7/8", # 2-5"x5 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, 602 (Office Copy), Order Number 6614, Drawing 2 (Folder 98)
        Plan and Scale Stonework for Music Room Mantel, 16 1/4"x24 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, 603 (Office Copy, Order Number 6614, Drawing 3 (Folder 98)
        Scale Layout and Full Size Details of Marble Base in Music Room, 26"x21", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        Approved by Jas Gamble Rogers 9/16/1920
      - 6/19/1908, 1021 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 58 (Folder 99)
        Plan of Marble Base Around Music Room, Section Thro' Marble Base, 25 1/2"x@ 26 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 99)
        Music Room Mantel, Harkness Residence, 14 3/8"x12", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
        Received 7/10/1920
      - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 99)
        Plan of Music Room, in 2 Pieces, Top Portion, 36 3/8"x@ 12", Bottom Portion, 36 3/8"x23 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Chas B. Mayer, Architectural Woodwork Corp.
  - HVAC, 4.2
    - 10/5/1982, AC-2, Job Number 26-82 (Folder 100)
      Proposed Air Conditioning System, Second Floor, 36 1/2"x20", Sepia Tone, Architects, P and O Air Control Co., Inc.
    - 4/9/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 100)
      Second Story Plan, Mezzanine Story Plan (In Second), Section Through Heat Flue in Wall, Notes on the Bottom, It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 3/8"x12 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A
  - Plumbing, 4.3
    - 4/15/1907, 1367 (Folder 101)
      Plumbing Plans, Second Story Plan, # 1-36 1/4"x15 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-20 1/2"x8 7/8", Paper, Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
  - Electrical, 4.4
    - undated, 18/2 (Folder 102)
      Detail of Ceiling in Library, Face View of Cast Iron Box Showing Receptacle in Place, 19 1/2"x17 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Lord Electric Company
    - 5/9/1908, 116 NY 33 (Folder 102)
      Revised Plan of Electric Work in Music Room, # 1-37 1/4"x27 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-36 3/8"x27 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 5/4/1908, 922 (Office Copy), Order Number 2047, 1824/10 (Folder 102)
      Panels A-, Aa, Ab and Ac 2nd Floor, Sheet Steel Box, Panels Ad, Ae, Af and Ag 2nd Floor, Sheet Steel Box, 15 1/2"x@ 13 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
    - 7/2/1908 (Revised), Order Number 2047, 1824/10 (Folder 102)
      Panel A, Aa, Ab, Ac, Ad, Ae, Af, Ag 2nd Floor, 15 1/2"x14 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
- Third Floor, 1906-1983; 5
  - Building/Floor Plans, 5.1
    - 11/8/1906, 4 NY 33 (Folder 103)
      Third Floor Plan, 41 3/4"x22, Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/29/1907, Revised 2/4/1908; 104 NY 33 (Folder 104)
      Third Story Plan and Fourth Story Plan, # 1-42 1/2"x32", Linen, # 2-42 3/8"x32 1/4, Diazo Blue Print, # 3-42 1/4"x32 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, #4-41 1/8"x32 1/2", Paper (Blue Ink), # 5-43 1/4"x32 1/2", Polyester Paper, # 6-21 1/4"x16 3/4", Paper (Photocopier Paper), Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/29/1907, 304 NY 33 (Folder 105)
      Boudoir-West Elevation, North Elevation, East Elevation and South Elevation, Bathroom "B"- West Elevation, South Elevation, and East Elevation, Chamber No. 2-North Elevation, East Elevation, South Elevation and West Elevation, (2) Owner's Chamber, Mrs. H's Dressing Room-West Elevation, North Elevation, East Elevation, and South Elevation, Bathroom "A"-West Elevation and East Elevation, # 1-42 1/4"x20 1/4", Linen, # 2-42 1/8"x20", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/29/1907, 305 NY 33 (Folder 105)
      Chambers No. 1-North Elevation, East Elevation, South Elevation, West Elevation, Valet's Room Fourth Floor-West Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation, Bathroom No. 1-Third Floor, Bathroom No. 2-Fourth Floor, Third Floor Valet's Room-North Elevation, East Elevation, West Elevations Maid's Room-East Elevation, West Elevation, South Elevation, Chamber No. 3-East Elevation, South Elevation, West Elevation, Chamber No. 4-East Elevation, South Elevation, West Elevation, Chamber No. 5-East Elevation, South Elevation, West Elevation, Chamber No. 6-North Elevation, East Elevation, South Elevation, # 1-42 1/8"x20 1/4", Linen, # 2-42"x20 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 6/22/1908, Revised 7/1/1908; 1023 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 59 (Folder 106)
      Plan of Fire Place Openings in Different Rooms, Chamber No. 3, Owner's Chamber, Owners Boudoir, # 1-13 3/8"x26 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Plans of Fire Place, Chamber No. 3, Owners Chamber, Owners Boudoir, 26 7/8"x10", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Draw of Fire Place Openings in Owner's Chamber, Boudoir and Chamber No. 3, 26 3/4"x10 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Boudoir
      - 2/5/1908, 363 NY 33 (Folder 107)
        Plan of Boudoir, Half Plan of Floor, Half Plan of Ceiling, General Note on Right Side, # 1-21"x21 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-20 7/8"x21 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 364 NY 33 (Folder 107)
        West Elevation of Boudoir, South Elevation of Boudoir, #1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together, 21 3/4"x26", Tracing Paper, # 2-21 3/4"x29 1/12", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-20 3/4"x25 7/8", Polyester Paper, #4-21 1/8"x25 7/8", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 365 NY 33 (Folder 108)
        North Elevation of Boudoir, East Elevation of Boudoir, # 1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together, 21 3/4"x25 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-29 3/4"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-21 "x26", Polyester Paper, #4-21 1/8"x25 3/4", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 794 (Office Copy), 360/6127 I (Folder 108)
        Boudoir, Ground Plan, 20 1/8"x25 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
        Received 4/4/1908 Charles T. Wills, 4/6/1908 Haleand Rogers
      - undated, 795 (Office Copy), 360/6127 M (Folder 108)
        Boudoir, West Elevation, 23 1/4"x16 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 796 (Office Copy), 360/6127K (Folder 109)
        Boudoir, South Elevation, 22"x16 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess andCo.
      - undated, 797 (Office Copy), 360/6127 L (Folder 109)
        Boudoir, East Elevation, 21 5/8"x16 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
      - undated, 798 (Office Copy), 360/6127 J (Folder 109)
        Boudoir, North Elevation, {Edges are cut on a diagonal} @ 21"x16 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
        Received 4/4/1908 Charles T. Wills, 4/6/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - 5/21/1908, 955 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 45 -Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy #) (Folder 109)
        Plan of Base in Boudoir, Section of Base, Third Floor, # 1-21 7/8"x17 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Detail of Base in Boudoir, Third Floor, 21 5/8"x18", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, /6127 (Folder 110)
        Line of Plaster Walls and Lower Line of Cornice, Written in Pencil on the Front, Boudoir, 12 7/8"x15 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, No Number Listed (Folder 110)
        Full Size Drawing of Window Panel Back Showing Registers, Full Size, Written on the Back in Pencil, FSD of Panel Backs Showing Registers In Boudoir, 3rd Floor, 28 1/4"x21 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
        Received 4/6/1908 Charles T. Wills
    - Owner's Chamber
      - undated, 360/6146'A' (Folder 111)
        Elevations of Grounds, North Wall Own Bedroom, 20"x11 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6146 'B' (Folder 111)
        Elevations of Grounds, East Wall Own Bedroom, 16 3/4"x11 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6146 'C' (Folder 111)
        Elevations of Grounds, South Wall Own Bedroom, 18 1/8"x11", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6146 'D' (Folder 111)
        Elevations of Grounds, West Wall Own Bedroom, 17 7/8"x11 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6146 'Q' (Folder 111)
        Ceiling Plan of Owner's Chamber, Written on the Back in Pencil, Hess's Drawing of Owner's Chamber Third Floor, @ 22 1/2"x35 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - 2/5/1908, 366 NY 33 (Folder 112)
        Plan, Owners Chamber, Half Plan of Floor, Half Plan of Ceiling, # 1-Paper Glued on Both Ends (Extenders), 27"x29 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-27 1/8"x20 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 367 NY 33 (Folder 112)
        South Elevation, Owners Chamber, General Note on the Right Side, # 1-27 3/8"x21 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-27 1/2x"21 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-26 1/2"x21 1/2", Polyester Paper, #4-26 1/2"x21 1/2", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 368 NY 33 (Folder 113)
        West Elevation, Owners Chamber, # 1-26 1/2"x21 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-26 3/4"x21 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-26 1/4"x21 1/2", Polyester Paper, # 4-26 1/2"x21 1/2", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 369 NY 33 (Folder 114)
        North Elevation, Owners Chamber, # 1-27 1/8"x21 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-27 1/4"x21 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-26 1/2"x21 1/2", Polyester Paper, #4-26 1/2"x21 3/8", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 370 NY 33 (Folder 115)
        East Elevation, Owners Chamber, # 1-27 5/8"x21 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-27 5/8"x21 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-26 1/2'x21 1/2", Polyester Paper, #4-26 1/2"x21 3/8", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 5/18/1908, 954 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 43 (Folder 116)
        Plan of Marble Base in Owner's Bedroom, Section of Base, 26"x17", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, No Number Listed (Area is Torn and Missing) (Folder 117)
        No Title, Torn and Missing, Written on the Back in Pencil, Hess's Drawings of Owner's Chamber Third Floor and ...s's Drawing of...Chamber...loor, (Soffit at West End of Room, East, Soffit at North and South Ends, Finished Plastered Ceiling), In 2 Pieces @ 41"x18 1/2" and @ 6 1/2"x6 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
    - Bathroom A and B
      - 2/1/1908, 357 NY 33 (Folder 118)
        Details of Bathroom "A", Third Story, Plan, Section Looking North, Section Looking South, Section Looking East, West Elevation, # 1-34"x22 1/4", Linen, # 2-22 3/8"x33 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/1/1908, 358 NY 33 (Folder 118)
        Detail of Bathroom "B", Third Floor, Plan and North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation, West Elevation, # 1-34"x22 1/2", Linen, # 2-22 5/8'x34 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 5/1908, 901 (Office Copy) Number 220 (Folder 118)
        Bathroom-A-Third Floor, 26 3/8"x27", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Chas T Wills, Inc. Builders, Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., Carrara Glass Department, Hale and Rogers
        Received 5/25/1908 Charles T. Wills, 5/26/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - 8/31/1908, No Number Listed (Folder 118)
        Revised Drawing of Nickel Plated Brass Ring for Jewelry Safe in Owner's Bathroom, Elevation, Section, Written on the Back in Pencil, Band for Safe in Bathroom 3 Floor, 14 1/2"x14 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
    - Valet's Room
      - 4/16/1908, 399-3 NY 33 (Folder 119)
        Scale of Full Size Details of Ceiling, Light in Valet's Room, Third Story, Plan of Ceiling Light, # 1-16 1/8"x22 3/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-22 5/8"x16 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 9/24/1908, 399-11 NY 33 (Folder 119)
        Case in Passage to Valet's Room, Third Story, Sliding Door and Shirt Drawer, Plan, Front Elevation, Plan, Section and Elevation of Divisions in Shirt Compartment, Full Size, # 1-24 1/2"x20", Tracing Paper, # 2- (1) 24 3/4"x13 3/4", (2) 24 3/4"x6 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Mrs. Harkness' Dressing Room
      - 2/5/1908, 371 NY 33 (Folder 120)
        Plan of Dressing Room, Third Story, Half Plan of Floor, Half Plan of Ceiling, # 1-21 7/8"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-22"x17 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 372 NY 33 (Folder 120)
        Dressing Room, Third Story, Half of South Elevation, West Elevation, Half of North Elevation, # 1-31 3/4"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-32"x17 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 4/30/1908-5/14/1908, 904 (Office Copy) (Folder 121)
        Full Scale Details of Radiator Enclosures in Dressing Room on 3rd Floor, Typical for All Enclosures, Section, Part Elevation, Part Plan, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Sutter's Detail of Radiator Enclosures, 41 1/8"x35", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, NY 33 904 Revised Radiator Enclosures, 41 3/4"x34 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, G.A. Suter and Co.
        #1-4/30/1908 #2-Revised 5/14/1908
      - undated, P-23, 768 (Folder 122)
        Plan, Dressing Room, Third Story, 20"x19 7/8", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co. (Much of the Name is Missing)
      - undated, P-24, 769 (Folder 122)
        Dressing Room Third Story, North Elevation, Elevation of Ends of Long Cases on East and West Walls, 20 3/4"x14", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, P-25, 770 (Folder 122)
        Dressing Room Third Story, West Elevation, 16 1/8"x14 3/8", Paper, Architects, N/A, (Probably Pottier and Stymus Co.)
      - undated, P-26, 77? (The Last Number is Missing-Probably a1) (Folder 122)
        Dressing Room, Third Story, South Elevation, Front Elevation of Case on Each Side of Wndow, 21"x14 1/4", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, P-27, 772 (Folder 122)
        Dressing Room, Third Story, East Elevation, 16 1/2"x14 3/4", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
    - Linen Closet
      - 5/5/1907, 399-5 NY 33 (Folder 123)
        Elevation of Case in Linen Closet, Third Story, Section B-B, Elevation of One Side of Linen Closet, Fourth Floor, Section A-A, # 1-30 3/8"x 17 1/2", Linen, # 2-30 3/8"x17 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Chamber No. 1/Bathroom No. 1
      - 2/1/1908, 359 NY 33 (Folder 124)
        Details of Bathroom No. 1, Third Story, Plan, North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation and West Elevation, # 1-34"x22 1/2", Linen, # 2-22 1/2"x34 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 373 NY 33 (Folder 124)
        Plan Chamber No. 1, # 1 -27 5/8"x19 5/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-27 5/8"x19 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 374 NY 33 (Folder 125)
        East Elevation, Chamber No. 1, # 1-26"x16 1/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-27 1/8"x16 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 375 NY 33 (Folder 125)
        Chamber No. 1, South Elevation, Half of North Elevation, # 1-27 1/8"x16 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-27 1/4"x16 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 376 NY 33 (Folder 125)
        West Elevation, Chamber No. 1, Note on the Right Side, # 1-27 1/8"x16 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-27"x16 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 7/1/1908, 399-7 NY33 (Second Copy Doesn't Have Drawing Number) (Folder 126)
        Details of Closets off Chamber No. 1 and No. 2, Section: A-A, B-B, C-C, D-D, E-E, F-F, H-H, K-K, Plan of Closet Off Chamber No. 1, Plan of Closet Off Chamber No. 2, Closet Off Chamber No. 1, Closet Off Chamber No. 2, # 1-48 1/8"x24 1/4", Linen, # 2- (2 Pieces) 1-@ 43 1/2"x24 1/4", 2-3 1/4"x5", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 8/24/1966, Order Number 589 (Folder 127)